(
"ai_sub_version": "3.6.0",
"generated_at": "2026-10-07T22:38:58.623270",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"service_tier": null,
"service_tier_subtitles": null,
"service_tier_lyrics": null,
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
携帯電話はマナーモードに設定し、録音・録画の禁止、席の移動はお控えください。
Set phones to silent, no recording allowed,
and please remain in your seats.
照明の点滅にご注意ください。改造・高輝度ペンライトの使用は禁止です。
Please be aware of flashing lights.
No modified or high-brightness light sticks.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
携帯電話はマナーモードに設定し、録音・録画の禁止、席の移動はお控えください。
Set phones to silent, no recording allowed,
and please remain in your seats.
照明の点滅にご注意ください。改造・高輝度ペンライトの使用は禁止です。
Please be aware of flashing lights.
No modified or high-brightness light sticks.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
ご来場のお客様へ：マナーモードの設定、撮影・録音の禁止、席移動の禁止
Attention: Please silence your phone, refrain from recording, and stay in your seat.
照明の点滅にご注意ください。改造・高輝度ペンライトの使用禁止。
Please watch out for flashing lights. No modified or high-brightness light sticks.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
ご来場のお客様へ：マナーモードの設定、撮影・録音の禁止、席移動の禁止
Attention: Please silence your phone, refrain from recording, and stay in your seat.
照明の点滅にご注意ください。改造・高輝度ペンライトの使用禁止。
Please watch out for flashing lights. No modified or high-brightness light sticks.
アーカイブ配信決定！
Archive streaming confirmed!
Archive stream confirmed!
首都高バトル
Tokyo Xtreme Racer
IRyS holoplus JACK 本日22:00まで
IRyS holoplus JACK (Until 22:00 today)
タレントの投稿＆高音質ボイス！ ホロプラス
Exclusive posts & high-quality voices! holoplus
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait.
携帯電話は電源を切るかマナーモードに設定してください
Turn off your smartphone or set it to silent mode.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait.
携帯電話は電源を切るかマナーモードに設定してください
Turn off your smartphone or set it to silent mode.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
ご来場のお客様へ
To our guests
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
ご来場のお客様へ
To our guests
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights
携帯電話は電源を切るかマナーモードに設定してください。撮影・録音・録画は禁止とさせていただきます。公演中は席の移動をお控えください。
Please turn off your phone or set to silent mode. Photography, recording, and videotaping are prohibited. Please refrain from moving from your seat.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください。改造ペンライトおよび、高輝度のペンライトはご使用いただけません。
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. No modified or high-brightness light sticks are permitted.
本日は、IRyS 1st Concert...
Today, IRyS 1st Concert...
HOPE...
Beyond the Stars にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Beyond the Stars! Thank you so much for coming!
すみません、Okay, okay. I'm going to read this, okay? Okay.
Excuse me, okay, okay. I'm going to read this, okay? Okay.
えっと、最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
Um, to ensure you enjoy the concert until the very end, I have a few announcements.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りしております。
Photography, recording, and the use of recording equipment during the performance are strictly prohibited.
館内はき、禁煙となっております。
The venue is non-smoking... non-smoking.
喫煙はご遠慮ください。No smoking! はい。
Please refrain from smoking. No smoking! Yes.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、無理をせず近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
If you feel unwell, please do not push yourself and let a nearby staff member know.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、
Moshing, diving, jumping excessively inside the venue,
ステージに物を投げ込むなど、ほかの皆さんに、
throwing objects onto the stage, and any other behavior that causes a nuisance to others
ご迷惑になったり、公演をさまたげ、さまたげる行為は一切禁止です。
or disrupts, disrupts the performance is strictly prohibited.
当たり前じゃないですか。はい。
Well, obviously! Yes.
ルールは、ルールは守って
Please follow the rules,
盛り上がってください。ね？
and have a great time, okay?
えーっと、演出の都合上、
Um, due to production reasons,
通路、通路にお荷物を置いたり、足を出したりしないようにしてください。
please do not leave your belongings or stick your legs out into the aisles.
また、本公演は
Also, for this performance,
映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場に入り、客席が映り込む場合はあります。はい。
cameras for video streaming and photography will be in the venue, so you may appear in them. Yes.
映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性はございますのであらかじめご了承ください。
Please understand that these videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes.
そしてみんな！
And everyone!
ペンライト持ってきてますか？
Did you bring your penlights?
えー、ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
今日はね、会場内に「この曲はこの色」みたいな
Today, recommended penlight colors like "this song is this color"
ペンライトカラーイメージが、左右のサービススクリーンとステージにあるモニターの一部に表示されます。
will be displayed on the side screens and some of the monitors on stage.
助かるよね、はい。
That's helpful, right? Yes.
えっと、みんな
So, everyone,
それに合わせてカラーを変更してくれたら嬉しいです。
I'd be happy if you could change your colors to match!
また、ライブのハッシュタグは、
Also, the hashtag for the live show is...
ハッシュタグ、アイリスコンサート2026です。
...hashtag IRySConcert2026!
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてください！
Please use the hashtag and post a lot to hype things up!
それでは、開演までもう少しです。
Well, it's almost time for the show to start.
みんなで一緒に盛り上がりましょう！
Let's get hyped up together!
アイリスでした！
This was IRyS!
はい、英語いきます。
Alright, going to do English now.
English next!
Thank you so much for joining me today
for IRyS's— my first concert, Hope Beyond the Stars!
Before we begin,
I have a few things I'd like to let you know so you can enjoy the concert to the fullest.
Photography and the use of audio or video
recording equipment are strictly prohibited during the performance.
Smoking is not permitted... per- per- permitted
inside the venue, so please refrain from smoking.
If you start feeling unwell, please don't push yourself.
Please let a staff member nearby know.
Moshing, stage diving,
jumping excessively, throwing things onto the stage,
and any other behavior that could disrupt other guests or disrupt the show are strictly prohibited.
Have fun and get hyped while following the rules!
For production and safety reasons,
please make sure not to leave any belongings in the aisles or stick your legs out into them, please.
In addition, cameras for video- video streaming
and photography will be operating inside the venue, so you may appear in the footage or photos.
These videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes, so please keep that in mind.
Thank you very much for your understanding.
And, everyone, did you all bring your light sticks?
During the concert, we'll be displaying the light stick color for each song on the side screens
and some of the monitors on stage. It's gonna show up like, you know, "this song is red, so it'll show up as red."
I'd love it if you could change your light stick colors to match them, please. And thank you!
And don't forget that the official hashtag for the concert is #IRySConcert2026.
Be sure to use it and help spread the excitement!
We're almost ready to get started.
Let's get excited and enjoy the concert together!
アイリスでした！
This was IRyS!
Should there be a spell that could grant my wishes
It would be you.
I will gift you with
Hope made of miracles.
Our journey towards Hope begins
Brazen fire
みんなー！IRySの1stソロコンサートに来てくれてありがとう！
Everyone! Thank you for coming to IRyS's 1st Solo Concert!
私とみんなで、忘れられない一日にしよう！
Let's make this an unforgettable day together!
What's up, IRystocrats? Are you ready for this?
Can't control it anymore, I'm burning up red
Crazy thoughts filling my head
Tension rising to the top, oh this night will never stop
Play with fire, it's getting hot, it's your fault, my baby
Fever burning...
...can't be contained
Set my heart on fire with a flame
Tell me you can feel the spirit in here
I don't wanna run away from this fight of fate
Caught in a heatwave, I'll never get enough
Fan the flame of love
Blazing fire, make me a believer
I'm getting dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burning like a fever
Come hold me closer if you dare
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Please love, burn me away
Blazing fire!
みんなで、一緒にいくぞー！
Everyone, let's go together!
はい！はい！はい！
Hey! Hey! Hey!
I'm gonna turn it up, I'm burning up
Can't get enough, maybe I'm too hot to touch
It's your fault, baby
I can't hide it anymore, I'm baring my soul
Let the flames swallow me whole
This is how we're gonna play a dangerous game
Fire, fire, running through my veins
Baby, can't you read between the lines
Spirit all away until the night
Caught in a heatwave, I'll never get enough
Fan the flame of love
Blazing fire, make me a believer
I'm getting dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burning like a fever
Come hold me closer if you dare
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Please love, burn me away
Blazing fire!
Jump! Jump! Jump! Jump!
I'm only getting started
Show me your illusion
It doesn't matter if it's real or a dream
Wild desire, fueling my delusion
I want you to burn with me
Blazing fire, make me a believer
I'm getting dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burning like a fever
Come hold me closer if you dare
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Please love, burn me away
Blazing fire!
Heart...
...stops
Breathe...
...out
Un-...
...lost
Breathe...
みんな、エスカレート！
Everyone, let's escalate!
さあ、まだまだ盛り上げていくよ！
Now, we're still gonna pump it up!
レッツ、エスカレート！
Let's escalate!
Born of another vortex
Shadowed with my regret
And I couldn't forget
The words ringing in my head
'Save such a wreck,' if you say so, I guess...
I am headed towards the fire
My head is clutching overdrive
Running straight into what they all said I can't do
Ready to burn, start this, it's my desire
Let's escalate!
Go ahead, don't overthink
Do what it takes till they all know your name
Singing your song, right toward defeat
But it's too late, because it's all yours to take
So ready or not, don't contemplate, live your life
There's just no...
Lagging behind the rest,
I made every excuse for running just on fumes.
I dreamed I could be the best.
I'll make it all come true, just wait and watch.
And if you turn off the cruise control,
forget about the limits now.
Oh, I'm finding my way inside my mind,
all the odds on our side,
ready to turn the cards,
strictly to find each part, there is no doubt.
So hit the gas, don't ever hit the brakes,
do what it takes until they know your name.
Dreaming of tomorrow, toward the fate,
rush into it, cause there's no youth to take, so ready, set, go!
No, don't contemplate, you'll waste your life,
there is just no time to wait.
You will never break, and it's no mistake
that you've got this far, don't you be afraid.
Oh...
I'll escalate it!
Ah...
Thank you so much!
Up past the limit, feel my heart rising.
Drifting away, I'm flying far,
my engines burning,
hotter than fire itself,
pushing to excel, all for myself,
and for you.
So hit the gas, don't ever hit the brakes,
do what it takes until they know your name.
Dreaming of tomorrow, toward the fate,
rush into it, cause there's no youth to take, so ready, set, go!
No, don't contemplate, you'll waste your life,
there is just no time to wait.
You will never break, and it's no mistake
that you've got this far, don't you be afraid,
hit the highway!
Believe and escalate!
Hey, going my way?
I'll get you where you need to be.
Ready? Let's hit the road!
If you look lonely, I caught you getting deep in despair.
Why don't you call me? You know I'm gonna answer your prayer.
We'll turn up the ignition,
I'll take you for a spin.
We don't even know where we're going.
You wanna bask in heaven's glow,
then stop, look out below.
I've kept the sky cuz I'm a star,
they call me Lyra, just a sign.
But I can be more, I gotta be more,
I know what I'm for.
Oh baby, I can be the girl of your dreams.
Oh baby, I'm a goddess on display.
So baby, baby, baby, treat me like a lady.
I'm the cure for your blues.
Oh baby, baby, baby, you're the one I choose.
Let me be your muse.
Now that you know all about me,
bet you can't live without me.
So come on and get me, baby,
and let me show you my speed, ah!
Chase me like the devil, with the pedal to the metal,
follow...
Follow me!
Our heavenly body, energy is high.
Tell me, honey, do you wanna know my sign?
Cause I could be an angel or a demon,
I'll let you dream it.
今日は一緒に最高のライブを
Today, we'll deliver the best live performance together,
届けていくバンドメンバーの紹介をするよ！
and I'm going to introduce our band members!
まずはベース！
First up, the bass!
ベース！高林カガヤン！
Bass! Kagayan Takabayashi!
ドラム！山本淳也！
Drums! Junya Yamamoto!
ギター！小迫竜介！
Guitar! Ryusuke Kosako!
キーボード、そしてバンドマスター、西村奈央！
Keyboard, and band master, Nao Nishimura!
そして、ダンサーズ！
And backup dancers!
All right!
Put those hands in the air!
All eyes on me!
Come on, let's go!
How sweet...
I can be the girl of your dreams
It's not bad
I've got a lot of things to say
So baby, baby, treat me like a leader
I'm the cure for your blues
Oh baby, baby, you're the one I choose
Won't you be my muse?
How sweet...
Yeah, let's party go!
Something is calling me tonight
Telling me that I have to protect
Steal your mind with song divine
I will shut up my inner conflict
harmony and chaos, let me be your muse
Hi! Hi, IRyS! It's IRyS from Hololive Promise!
Thank you so much for coming!
Thank you so much for being here today to my very first solo live concert, "Hope Beyond the Stars"!
IRySの初めてのソロライブ、Hope Beyond the Starsに来てくださり、ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming to IRyS's very first solo live, Hope Beyond the Stars!
いやー、いよいよ始まっちゃった。
Wow, it's finally started.
It started! Oh my god! This is so surreal! I've been preparing, but I'm just like, "Wait, what do you mean I'm doing it right now?"
なんかやっているっていうのが、もう信じられないんですけど、本当にありがとうございます。嬉しいです。
I can't believe I'm actually doing this right now, but thank you so much. I'm so happy.
一応あの、待ちに待ったね、ファーストライブ！
Finally, our long-awaited first live concert!
「夢は奇跡じゃない、みんなで起こす魔法」をテーマに、
With the theme, "Dreams aren't miracles, they're magic we create together,"
みんなに立たせてもらったこのライブを、最高にする魔法をかけたいと思っています。
I want to cast a spell to make this live concert you built for me the absolute best.
I am going to cast a spell on all of you today. "A magical night" — that's the theme of this live. Yay!
I can see all of you! みんな見えているよ！
I can see all of you! I can see everyone!
Oh my god, there are so many people! There are so many people! Thank you!
本当にね、披露したい楽曲がね、もうとにかくね、ありすぎて、全部詰め込んだら、とにかくすごいセットリストの曲数になっちゃいました！
Honestly, there were so many songs I wanted to perform that when I crammed them all in, the setlist ended up with an incredible number of tracks!
はい！えっと、みんな最後まで楽しんで、ついてきてくれると嬉しいです。
Yes! So I'd be so happy if you enjoy yourselves and keep up with me until the very end.
I have a lot of original songs, and I tried to fit as many as I can, and from that, it's a pretty long setlist. Yay!
So, you know, you guys might get tired midway, but I hope you guys, you know, keep the energy up until the very end!
ね、みんなも途中で疲れちゃった、とかになるかもしれないけど、ぜひね、IRySと一緒に最後まで駆け抜けましょう！
Yeah, you might get tired halfway through, but please run through to the very end with IRyS!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ではね、今日は会場... 会場、ね、この曲はこの色、そう、あの、この曲はこの色って、さっきあの...
And so, today the venue... the venue... for this song, it's this color. Yes, for this song, it's this color... earlier...
ましたよね？
...right?
見えました？
Did you see it?
Did you guys see the prompt
to change to this color
on the... on the monitors?
Yeah! Are you guys following it?
みんな、言うこと聞いてます？
Is everyone following it?
あのプロンプトの...
That prompt's instructions...
聞いてくれると嬉しいな、もちろんね。
I'd be happy if you do, of course.
あの、反抗したい気持ちもまあね、
I know some of you might want to rebel,
多少あるのはわかるんですけど。
and I can understand that too.
はい、えっと、そうね。
But anyway, yes.
この曲はこの色！みたいな、
For "this song, use this color!"
ペンライトカラーイメージが左右のサービスモニター
The suggested penlight colors are on the side monitors
と、ステージモニターの一部に
and on parts of the stage monitors.
表示されてます。今回、ちょっと新しいチャレンジだと思います、ホロでは。
This is a new experiment for Hololive, I believe.
So, this is the first time, I think, we're trying out...
...using penlight colors on the sides,
like showing, 'Oh, what penlight color for what song?' on all the monitors.
So, if you're curious, or you don't know...
'What color should I turn on?'
then you follow the monitor, it says the color.
Yeah!
助かるよね？
It helps, right?
Yeah! 良かった。
Yeah! Glad to hear.
えっとね、ちなみに
By the way, did everyone
私のファーストアルバム「Dystopia」、
listen to my first album, "Dystopia"...
みんな聞いてくれた？
Did you all listen to it?
良かった！
Awesome!
I'm glad you guys listened to my first album that came out, like, a bit ago, a few months ago.
あ、ね、今回はね、あの、そちらのアルバムからもちろん
And for this concert, of course, from that album,
たくさんの楽曲を、今日、披露しようかなと思ってます。
I'm going to perform a lot of songs today.
I'm going to showcase a lot of songs from that album.
Of course, I will also still be showcasing a lot of songs from past
EPs and what not too, obviously.
そう、そう、そう。もちろん、あの、過去のね、EPとか
Yes, yes. Of course, I've picked some songs
シングルからも、もちろん曲ピックアップしてるんで
from my past EPs and singles too,
その辺も楽しみにしててください。
so please look forward to those as well!
えっと、はい。
Alright, yes.
ちなみに、ね、今回は今日はね、ユーロビートからバラードまで、色んなジャンルをね、
By the way, today we'll be performing various genres,
あの、披露しようかなと思ってます。
from Eurobeat to ballads.
I'm going to have, of course, the Eurobeat songs, which, you know, you guys heard some of it already,
and some ballady, more, you know, soft songs in the setlist as well, so please enjoy the variety.
あの、しかも、今日は...
And what's more, today...
生バンドでお届けしてます！
We're performing with a live band!
いや、本当にありがたい、ありがたいし、もう光栄です！
I'm so incredibly grateful and honored!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
Thank you so much to the band members, and...
It still feels surreal to be able to perform with a live band, oh my goodness!
Thank you so much!
えっと、リハの時からね、もう、とにかく興奮が止まらなくて、
Ever since rehearsals, I couldn't stop being excited,
早くみんなにお届けしたかったんです！
and I wanted to perform for everyone as soon as possible!
I've been wanting to perform for you guys with this live band for ages, so I'm really glad we're finally able to do it! Yeah!
So, I hope you guys enjoy this till the very end.
さてね、えっと、この、
Now, as for this...
この、今回のね、ライブですが、
As for this concert...
えっと、ライブの感想をぜひハッシュタグ...
Please share your thoughts on the live with the hashtag...
あ、アイリス、まあここにハッシュタグがある、多分ないだろうな、今回は。
Oh, IRyS, well there's a hashtag here... probably not this time.
あの、ハッシュタグね、
Anyway, please use the hashtag
「#アイリスコンサート2024」で
#アイリスコンサート2024
たくさんポストしてくれると嬉しいです。みんなで盛り上げましょう。
and post a lot! Let's hype this up together!
Please use the hashtag...
...for, uh, watching this, this live,
use the hashtag #IRySConcert2024, yeah, post it on SNS! Let's all hype it up! Yeah!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
さあ、そして、
Now, then...
I think you guys probably noticed by... probably, you know, そろそろそのタイミングだよねっていう、
I think you guys probably noticed... probably, you know, it's about that time.
えっと、そして、はい。
And, yes...
まだ言ってないよ！
I haven't said it yet!
YouTube, TikTokでご覧の方はこのMCパートで終了です。
For those watching on YouTube and TikTok, the free part ends after this MC.
イェーイ！
Yay!
「えー」って、「えー」って言ってる人。
I hear some of you going "Ehh?"
まあ、でもみんな会場にいるから関係ないよね？でも、あの、配信のみんな！
Well, you guys are here at the venue, so it doesn't matter, right? But to those watching the stream!
配信のみんな！
Everyone on stream!
I can see you guys! Yeah!
Free part ending. Yes, it's ending after this.
あ、まだまだね、一緒に盛り上がりたいみんなは、
But if you still want to keep hyping it up together,
概要欄から配信、配信のチケットのね、リンクがあるんで、
there's a link to the streaming ticket in the description,
踏んで買ってね！
so click it and buy one!
Yeah, buy... uh, yeah, free part is ending,
but if you guys are interested, if you guys want to see the rest of this concert,
you can get the... you can get the streaming ticket from the link in the description of what you're watching, whether it's YouTube or TikTok.
Yeah! Buy it! Yeah! Buy!
はい、ぜひ買ってね。はい。
Yes, please buy it. Yes.
みんな、あと、今回は、えっと、ステージ固定カメラ、そう！言うの忘れた。
Also, everyone, this time there's a fixed stage camera! Oh, I forgot to mention.
えっと、ステージ固定カメラも、つい、あ、ついてるんじゃなくて、あの、追加でね、追加料金で買えます。凄いよね！
You can purchase the stage fixed camera option as an add-on. That's amazing, right?
Yeah, there's also a staged fixed camera view of the concert for streaming tickets.
You can add it as an add-on to your regular streaming ticket.
Yeah, isn't that nice? That means you get to see everything, like me, yeah! The whole time.
ずっとね。
The whole time.
アイリスの動きが全部見られますよ、それで。
You can see all of IRyS's movements that way.
すごいよね。はい。
It's amazing, isn't it? Yes.
なので、ぜひ、あの、結構おトクな追加のコンテンツなので、
So, it's a pretty good deal for extra content,
ぜひ、ご検討よろしくお願いします。
so please do consider it.
さて、まだまだライブは始まったばっかりですからね。
Well then, the concert has only just begun!
早速、次の曲… ちょっとその前にお水飲んでいいですか？
Let's get right to the next song... Wait, can I drink some water first?
「がんばれ」ありがとう。Thank you. はい、じゃあ次の曲。
Thank you for cheering me on. Thank you. Okay, now for the next song.
えっと、すごく、あの、爽やかな…
It's a very refreshing...
爽やかというか、もうしっとりめのバラード、行きたいと思ってます。
Actually, more like a gentle... a gentle ballad.
すごく私にとって大事な曲で、so it's going to be a ballad song that is really important to me.
It's a very important song to me, so it's going to be a ballad song that is really important to me.
Please listen to... 「心臓が止まるまで」、ぜひ聴いてください。
Please listen to... "Until My Heart Stops."
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました。
[On-Screen Text: The preview has ended. Thank you for watching.]